Congratulations on making it this far.
恭喜你终于学到这一阶段了
The content you've seen previously,
之前学习的内容
will serve as a strong foundation of knowledge
将为你成为一名量化分析师
from which to build your quantitative finance career.
打下扎实的基础
We have a few more concepts to discuss.
我们还要讨论一些概念
But before we get into the weeds,
但在学习具体知识之前
let's take this opportunity to step back for a moment.
先回头总结一下
I want to describe the series of steps,
我将大致描述下定量分析师
quants go through when developing trading strategies from a big picture of perspective.
在制定交易策略时执行的步骤
So you'll be able to see,
使你能够明白
how each step can contribute to
每一步对实现最终目标的作用
the ultimate goal of profiting from a successful trading strategy.
即通过成功的交易策略获利
This will help you understand the point of each school year learning and
这样有助于你理解所学的知识
make concepts discussed in the next few videos more clear.
并且使接下来的几个视频中讨论的概念更清晰
Fundamentally, quantitative trading is the process of using statistical analysis and
从根本上来说 量化交易是指
modeling to predict market behavior and using
利用统计学分析和建模预测市场行为
those predictions to make trades with the goal of profit.
并利用这些预测进行交易从而获利的流程
Like any research process understanding and predicting
和任何研究流程一样 理解和预测市场行为
market behavior begins with a new idea for how the world might work.
首先需要对市场的运行方式有新的理解
In other words, a hypothesis.
也就是说 做出假设
A good hypothesis is the first step to making predictions about future behavior.
好的假设是预测未来行为的第一步
Coming up with a good hypothesis means being brutally specific.
好的假设必须非常具体
For example, the hypothesis stocks that are discussed in
例如“在新闻中讨论的股票很有可能会上涨”
the news are likely to go up is not very useful by itself,
这个假设本身用处不大
because it's so vague that it doesn't lead to testable predictions.
因为这个假设太模糊了 不能得出可检验的预测
In what news outlet?
是哪个新闻机构？
At what time?
在什么时间？
In what manner must the stocks we discussed and for how long will they go up?
以什么形式讨论股票？股价将上涨多久？
An improved hypothesis would be stocks whose company name or ticker
改进后的假设可以是
appear in the landing page of
“如果公司名称或代码出现在
The Wall Street Journal website will increase by price by one percent,
《华尔街日报》网站登陆页上
one day following this appearance.
那么股价将在此新闻出现后的第二天上涨 1%”
Although it's far from perfect,
虽然这个假设很不靠谱
we can actually test this hypothesis by
但是我们实际上可以检验此假设
finding the tickers and checking for the change in price.
我们可以找到该股票代码并看看它的价格变化
So how do you come up with a good hypothesis?
如何提出好的假设？
Well, your hypothesis should be based on your current understanding of how markets work.
应该根据你对市场运行原理的理解提出假设
So the more you know about the markets,
所以对市场越了解
the more likely you are able to come up with a new potentially profitable idea.
越有可能想出可能会获利的新观点
It can take time to build up the domain knowledge to come up with
在任何研究领域 积累领域知识并提出好的假设
a good hypothesis in any field of study and quantitative finance is no exception.
都需要一定的时间 量化金融也不例外
So how do you build up this domain expertise?
如何掌握领域知识呢？
Well, you can try to immerse yourself in the markets,
你可以沉浸到市场中
observe the markets, watch financial news,
观察市场 看财经新闻
read financial newspapers, read books, read blogs,
阅读财经报纸 图书 博客
and study the known strategies of famous quants and discretionary traders and investors.
研究著名定量分析师和任意交易者及投资者的策略
Attend meetings and conferences and read
参加会议 阅读学术论文
academic papers such as those on the Social Science Research Network.
例如 Social Science Research Network 上的论文
An online repository of scholarly research in
这是一个涵盖社会科学领域的学术研究论文在线资源库
the social sciences including economics and finance.
包括经济与金融领域
But no matter who you are or what you know,
无论你是谁 或具备哪些知识
if your hypothesis makes predictions that are inconsistent with the real observed data,
如果你的假设做出的预测与真实数据不一致
your hypothesis is wrong.
你的假设就错了
The precise manner in which it is wrong,
到底是什么错误 何时错了？
when and how, we'll show you how to focus your efforts to improve it.
我们将从这些方面指导你改进假设